Build a 500mm x 900mm board to make a small quilt
Rotate the quilt and let it be simulated on the ground
Cut a layer to make the inflow effect, turn the surface over and let the front face all the way out
Then select these two front and back panels
Put pressure on the front and back panels
Set pressure to 3 to make the inflow effect
If the inflow is slower, you can take off some panels manually to make the inflow more obvious
Because we are making the quilt inside, the pressure 3 inflow is too obvious, so reduce it to 2
Change the shape of the fabric line to Custom Angle
We need to make the curves more smooth on the sides
Cut a layer to make the plate of the quilter be fit on the outside of the original plate
Save some steps
Then remove the joint of the newly created board and delete the sewing line
Because the board has been turned over on the surface, so if the sewing line is not certain, you can separate the two boards and sew them with the sewing tool in the 3D window
Then turn on the simulation
When the outer layer is smaller than the inner layer, the outer layer will be deformed, so it can be placed on the outer layer
When the outer layer is smaller than the inner layer, the outer layer can be placed on the outer layer
When there is two layers of boards, if the deformation is greater, it may be due to the wire gap cannot be penetrated
So it is necessary to get back to the starting point, the outer layer is only a little narrower
The center point of the double machine frame can activate center point function, and the following adjustments are based on the center point
I will explain it in more detail later
The outer layer of the back cover has been molded before, so it has the pressure of the original version, so you need to adjust the pressure of the outer layer to 0, because the back cover is usually single-layer and has no inflow.
If the back cover is pressed because of the pressure of the outer version, you can increase the pressure to 3.
Add a new fabric and drag it to the selected panel, and apply the new fabric to the small quilt panel.
Change the fabric to silk taffeta, which is a kind of synthetic fabric, which is easy to come out.
Reduce the density of this fabric to make the weight of the panel lighter and easier to create the fluffy feeling of the quilt.
Copy the inner fabric and increase the friction coefficient, so that when you make some random creases in the subsequent manual drag fabric, the creases will not dissipate due to the sliding of the fabric.
Close the mat to make the desktop look more magnificent.
Now we can place the curtain under the cover, and attach the most important part of the pápi.
Lay the curtain on the back of the quilt at an angle at 1.5 inches, and push the pattern to the front from both sides.
You will get this pattern shown earlier.
Place the curtain on the top of the pillow and press this moment to the top.
You can place the curtain over the block of the quilt and press it to the back of the pillow.
By doing this, the pattern of curtain will be better.
After you've placed the curtain on the back of the quilt, you can place the curtain on the top of the quilt, so that it will be easier to choose the draught.
Contrary to the way of making the curtain, you can place the curtain on the back of the pillow.
Turn the cup by hand to let the cup be in the right position
If the simulation speed is slow, you can press the simulation button to change to GPU simulation to deal with this part
Reduce the example time to 8 to make it more detailed
After adjusting to the right position, press the W key to click on the tabletop
You can click on the tabletop again
Add a fixed needle to the position of the tabletop to fix the small cup
After removing, pause the simulation and add a needle to maintain the effect of the fold before the fold disappears
The basic adjustment is that the friction coefficient of the surface is relatively high
If the friction coefficient is not high, the fold will soon disappear
And the fold will be more stable
In addition, it is easy to slip under GPU simulation
The fold will disappear when the friction coefficient is 30
Press the W key to click on the fixed needle again to delete the fixed needle
Thanks for watching
to get rid of more creases.
Add some fixed creases to the position needle.
After the simulation is stable,
return to the default simulation tool
and simulate again.
After that, we can select these panels,
and delete the fixed creases on the panels
in the menu on the right.
When the simulation has stopped,
we can continue with the simulation.